Since January, the president's bought more than $100 million worth of corporate and municipal
bonds. That is according to filings from the Office of Government Ethics. This kind of active
trading by a president is unprecedented. It means Donald Trump stands to benefit or suffer losses,
depending on how these bonds perform. But these bonds include banks and they include companies
and they include local governments that are literally directly impacted by the decisions
that Donald Trump is making in the White House. Tim, is this classic Donald Trump? You are
extremely familiar with how this gentleman works as a businessman. Well, it's not even Donald
Trump working as a businessman. It's Donald Trump working as an insider trader. It's Donald Trump
in a position to influence the interest rates that determine the value of the bonds he's buying.
It's that simple. The other thing is, it is a drop in the bucket. The $100 million in bonds he bought
is a drop in the bucket in terms of the grift that's going on in the White House around
cryptocurrencies. His net worth, I think, jumped by more than $2.5 billion based on paper, but it's
on cryptocurrency assets he holds at a time when his family had absolutely no experience in the
business before he became president. It's a product that he disparaged as a scam before he became president.
All right.
Do you know that?
Do you know what that brings to the store?